这下悲剧了
Well, this is awful.
真不敢相信查莉的生日要在监狱里度过了
I can't believe we're spending Charlie's birthday in jail.
好了  既然我们都在这里
Well, as long as we're all in here together,
那我们就重申下一些准则
let's go over some ground rules.
这只是一把椅子
This is just a chair.
-但  如果我  -不成
-Well, what if I... -Uh-uh.
-如果  -打住
-What if... -Hold it.
两位  还有更糟的呢
Guys, it could be worse.
老爸老妈会知道我们在这里的
Mom and dad could know we're here.
-孩子们  -惨了
-Kids? -Uh-oh.
好啊  老妈  好啊  老爸
Hi, mom. Hi, dad.
-好  -都好
-Hi. -Hey.
这下全家团聚了
Nice family you got here.
你们家的狗是不是也被抓进笼子里了
I'm guessing the dog is in the pound?
我们家没狗  “史努提”长官
We don't have a dog, officer "snootee."
是“史努忒”
It's pronounced "snoo-tay."
-你俩快进去吧  -给你
-Get in there, you two. -Here.
你们这仨小鬼在这里干嘛
What are you guys doing here?
你们这俩老鬼在这里干嘛
What are <i>you guys</i> doing here?
别吵了  在我们争论那问题之前
Okay, before we get to that,
我们还是再来重申下准则吧
let's go over the ground rules again.
老爸  尤其是你要注意听了
Dad, I want you to pay extra close attention.
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
■
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z  没有昵称
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
■
校订： line
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  追忆似水年华
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第一集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E01  Charlie is 2
我的孩子们在监狱里
So my kids are in jail.
有谁能给我解释下吗
Anybody wanna tell me why?
没人  我们挺好的
Nope, we're good.
好了  那你们呢  你们怎们进来的
Well, what about you? Why are you guys in jail?
嘿  我们先问的  请先回答我们
Hey, we asked you first. Start talking.
好吧  作为老大
All right well, as the oldest
我会给你们一个合理的解释
I guess I owe you guys an explanation.
这全是泰迪的错
It's all Teddy's fault.
-什么  你胡说  -噢  是吗
-What? It is not! -Oh really?
如果你没有承诺给查莉买一个
We wouldn't be here
你完全支付不起的生日礼物
if you hadn't promised Charlie
我们就不会在监狱里了
a birthday present you couldn't deliver.
查莉  快看啊
Well, Charlie, here you are,
这是你最喜欢的电视节目《咯咯笑》
watching your favorite tv show, "the gurgles."
这就是我们的声音
<i>That's the sound we make</i>
如果你够乖
<i>If we march in circles</i>
和我们一起兜圈圈
<i>and watch you play along</i>
那就快坐下  给妈妈捣捣乱
<i>Just sit down, annoy your mom</i>
一起唱咯咯歌  咯咯笑
<i>and sing the gurgle song, gurgles!</i>
有点闹心
It's kind of annoying,
不过我猜这和你的胃口
but I guess it's entertaining to your little brain.
噢  是《咯咯笑》  我都错过什么了
Oh, "the gurgles!" What did I miss?
-我喜欢咯咯笑  -嘘
-I love gurgles. -Shh!
如果我们比比看  是谁能够送给查莉
So if we're having a contest for who gives Charlie
有史以来最棒的生日礼物
the best birthday present ever,
那我就赢定了
I'll accept my prize now.
是吗  我可是送给了她生命
Okay well, I gave her the gift of life,
那你又送给了什么
so let's see what you got.
我送给她咯咯笑的演唱会门票
I'm getting her tickets to the gurgles concert.
-噢  -没错
-Oh! -Yeah.
我要让她度过超完美的两岁生日
I want her to have a great second birthday,
不像我当年  都是些我不想要的礼物
unlike mine when I didn't get the gift I wanted.
又来了  一直抱怨那只哈罗小狗
Here we go, still whining about a hello doggy.
是你好狗狗
Howdy puppy,
是西部最最可爱的吉娃娃
the rootinest tootinest little chihuahua in the West.
在这个世界上  我只想要他
I wanted him more than anything in the world
还有...
and I...
噢  现在说这个为时过早
Oh, too soon.
嘿  你觉着来场派对怎么样
Hey, how are you coming with the entertainment?
派对  派对吗
Entertainment. Entertainment?
查莉的生日派对
For Charlie's birthday party.
-你准备了什么  -啊
-What did you decide on? -Ah.
仍在考虑酝酿中
Still thinking. Noodling.
文思如泉涌啊
A lot of things going on in the old hopper.
泉已经枯竭了  对吧  鲍伯
The hopper's empty, isn't it, Bob?
我  我甚至都不知道那东西在哪里
I... I don't even know where it is anymore.
亲爱的  查莉的派对三天后就要举行了
Honey, Charlie's party is in three days.
好了  亲爱的  放轻松  我会想办法的
Oh, honey, come on, relax. I'll think of something.
好了  我们弄个小丑
Okay, we'll do a clown,
再弄个充气蹦床  什么的
a bouncy house... whatever.
鲍伯  亲爱的  你还是自己留着那些东西吧
Bob, honey, you have to reserve those things.
我们要弄些真正好的东西
We have to decide on something good
要不然哈罗小狗事件又要重演了
or it's gonna be hello doggy all over again.
是你好狗狗
<i>Howdy puppy!</i>
-嘿  能让我查看下邮件吗  -不成
-Hey, can I check my email? -No no no no no.
我要在线抢购咯咯笑的演唱会门票
I'm about to buy gurgles concert tickets online.
八秒钟之后  会开始网上销售
They go on sale in eight seconds
看我怎么抢下第一张票的
and I'm gonna be the first one to get them.
好了  准备  三  二  一
Okay, here we go. Three, two, one.
搞什么  已售罄
What? Sold out?!
开什么国际玩笑
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me.
别放弃  让我试试看
Hang on. Let me get in there.
等着瞧好吧
Let's see.
-你在干嘛  -查看邮件啊
-What are you doing? -Checking my email.
什么  给我
What? Give me that.
我该怎么弄到票呢
How am I gonna get the tickets now?
那个  前几天我在听
Well, the other day I was listening
儿童广播  KIDZ
to that radio station for kids, K.I.D.Z....
嘿  是儿童  我才搞明白
Hey, kidz. I just got that.
为什么你要听儿童广播
Why are you listening to the kidz radio station?
因为他们说不要转台
Because they told me not to change the channel.
总之  他们有个比赛
Anyway, they're having a contest.
拍出最佳视频的人可以获得咯咯笑的演唱会门票
Whoever makes the best video wins tickets to the gurgles concert.
我们可以拍出好的视频
We could make a great video.
我们只需要一个好点子
All we need is one good idea.
好吧  听听这个
Oh okay, how about this?
我们就拍
So we make a video of me putting on
我穿两百条内裤的视频
200 pairs of underpants.
然后我转过身  屁股上有几个大字
And then I turn around and on my butt it says.
“我爱咯咯笑”
"I heart the gurgles."
好了  审批不通过
Yeah, that's not it.
我  我也想到一个点子
I've... I've got an idea.
我写一些关于儿童的歌曲
I've written some really great kid songs.
我们可以将其中一首放在视频里
We could turn one of those into a video.
我需要一个好点子  只需一个啊
One good idea. Just one good idea.
我有一首歌是关于会说话的脚趾头
I have got a song about talking toes
你绝对会从头到脚的爱上他
that will knock your socks off.
懂了没  因为...算了
You get it? 'Cause it... okay.
好了  现在出来的全是馊点子
Okay, we're still going through all the bad ideas.
但我们需要金点子
But we need a good one,
而且应该让查莉成为其中的卖点
and Charlie should be the star of it.
我一直想把查莉从火炮中发射出去
Well, I've always wanted to shoot her out of a cannon.
成了  馊点子继续往外冒
All right, still emptying out all those bad ideas, okay.
火炮不成  内裤不成
No cannons? No underpants?
你们真是不懂我的良苦用心
You're really tying my hands here.
嘿  嘿  亲爱的  亲爱的
Hey hey, honey! Honey!
嘿  过来  进来  来
Hey, come on. Come in here. Come on.
-我给你看样东西  -什么东西啊
-I've got something I wanna show you. -What is it?
我给你展示下我为查莉生日派对准备的东西
I wanna show you the entertainment I got for Charlie's party.
看看吧
Voila.
一辆黄包车
A little cart.
难道是你来拉这辆车吗
This is why I'm missing "judge ira"?
天啊  我好像应该把黄包车挂在
Oh my, I seemed to have put the cart before the...
一匹马后面
Horse!
确定这是一匹马吗
Are you sure it's a horse?
我见过比这还大的狗
I've seen bigger dogs.
说实话  比这大的猫我都见过
Actually, I've seen bigger cats.
亲爱的  这是迷你马
Honey, it's a miniature horse.
不过  他还是挺可爱的
Well, he is kind of cute.
-你是从哪弄来的  -在马厩里
-Where did you find him? -At the stables.
告诉你  我本来想弄匹小马驹
You know, I was gonna get a pony,
但随后我在停车场发现了这家伙
and then I met this guy in the parking lot
有个人说“咱们做笔交易吧”
who said, "Have I got a deal for you."
接着我说“不用了  谢谢”
And well, after I said "no thank you" to the speakers,
随后他就把这匹马牵出来了
<i>he brought out</i> <i>shamrock here.</i>
他真是可爱
Aw, he's adorable.
为什么他的尾巴翘起来了
Why is his tail going up?
噢
Oh.
太好了
That was great.
嘿  妈  我们刚完成了视频拍摄
Hey, mom, we finished the video.
-想看看吗  -噢  太好了
-You wanna see it? -Oh, can't wait.
太好了  门票我们赢定了
Yeah, we are so gonna win those tickets.
咯咯笑
Gurgles!
■
咯咯笑访谈
晚上好
Good evening.
今天做客的是咯咯笑的最忠实的粉丝
I'm here with the world's biggest gurgles fan,
夏洛特·邓肯小姐
miss Charlotte Duncan.
噢不要  请叫我查莉
Oh no, please call me Charlie.
不要太客套
We're all friends here.
那么  查莉  告诉我们你是如何
So, Charlie, tell me how you first
知道咯咯笑的
became acquainted with the gurgles.
其实  我当时是十七...不  是十八个月大的时候
Well, I was 17... no, 18 months
当时我正在换频道找节目看
and I was doing a little bit of channel surfing.
那些无聊的节目啊
<i>Boring, blah.</i>
不是去过的就是看过的  突然
Been there, seen that. Then ba-bam!
这世上最美妙的画面映入我的眼帘
The most wonderful collection of shapes and colors.
-我从未看过  -咯咯笑
-I had ever seen. -The gurgles.
必须是咯咯笑
The gurgles indeed.
看他们的演唱会可以让我感觉到...
And seeing them in concert would make me feel...
好了  还是用行动来表达吧
Well, why don't I just show you?
灯光
Lights, please.
-哇  快看啊  -太棒了
-<i>Wow, look at this.</i> -<i>Cool.</i>
哇
Wow!
原谅我  我刚才有点激动
Forgive me. I got a bit carried away.
如果现在采访结束了
Now if we're done here,
有人答应要给我一盒果汁的
I was promised a juice box.
结束
■
你们真是太有才了
You guys, that was amazing!
噢  老妈  是你生出了个有才的查莉
Oh, mom, you made a brilliant Charlie.
噢  难道不是吗
Oh, didn't I?
演得不错  演得不错
Good show, good show.
再放一遍
Again.
-是吗  -是的
-Yes? -Yeah.
嘿  亲爱的  你看见车库遥控器了吗
Hey, honey, you seen the garage door opener?
不用找了
Never mind.
你搞什么
What are you doing?
有只迷你马在我们的车库里
There's a mini-horse in our garage.
你不觉着我应该好好利用下吗
Did you really think I wouldn't take advantage of that?
你去哪了
Where did you go?
去奥斯丁家了
Just down the street to Austin's house.
当时他正吹嘘他新买的狗
He's been bragging about his new dog.
这立马让他哑口无言了
This shut him right up.
好了  你能先下来吗
All right, come on. Get out of there, would you?
好吧
Okay.
噢  给你
Oh, here. There you go.
-这是什么  -门票啊
-What is this? -Tickets.
你不知道开小马车发短信也要挨罚单吗
Did you know you can't text while riding a mini-horse?
-哦 盖比  -什么事儿
- Uh, Gabe - Yep?
-你忘了某事吧  -噢  没错
- You forgetting something? - Oh right.
嘿  现在三点了
Hey, it's 3:00.
获奖视频现在应该公布了
The winning video should be up by now.
我这就去看
I'm on it
嘿  PJ  原来你今天还要上班啊
Hey, P.J. I didn't know you were working today.
不上  这是我唯一一件干净的T恤
I'm not. This is my only clean shirt.
还有你为什么戴着这顶帽子
Then why are you wearing the hat?
只穿工作T恤还真挺蠢
I don't wanna look stupid.
噢看啊  有结果了  他们登出了获奖视频
Oh, it's up. They've posted the winning video.
天啊  我紧张得都不敢看了
Oh, I can't look.
快啊  告诉我我们赢了  告诉我我们赢了
Okay, tell me we won. Tell me we won.
你怎么还没告诉我我们赢了
Why aren't you telling me we won?
-因为我们输了  -什么  不可能啊
- Because we lost. - What? I don't believe it.
哪一个视频会可能比我们更好
What video could possibly be better than ours?
获奖视频
■
知道我有多爱咯咯笑组合吗
How much do I love the gurgles?
裤爱
恐怕此时
Now at this point
某蠢人不得不说"我早告诉过你"
a jerk might say "I told you so."
没错  我早告诉过你
I told you so!
那我们该怎么办呀
So now what are we gonna do?
去市中心的皮埃蒙特酒店
Go downtown to the piedmont hotel
咯咯笑组合就住那儿  问他们去讨票好了
where the gurgles are staying and beg them for tickets?
你怎么会知道他们住哪儿
How do you know where they're staying?
"咯咯笑粉丝网"上面写的
It was on the "all things gurgles" website.
不会只有我一人知道这消息吧
Am I the only one who reads that?
是的是的  因为你是他们粉丝中
Yes yes, because you're their only fan
唯一识字的
that can actually read.
你真的以为去敲他们的房门
So you're just gonna knock on their door
他们就能放你进去吗
and they're gonna let you in?
会的  只要我们
They will if we're delivering
送他们桶鲜香炸鸡排
a delicious bucket of chicken.
要么就送你干外卖时送的那玩意儿吧
Or that stuff you deliver.
好主意  我们这就出发
Great! Let's go.
慢着  你们怎么知道
Wait a minute. How are you gonna know
-他们住哪间房  -423
- what room they're in? - 423.
我可是"咯咯笑粉丝网"的高级会员
I'm an "all things gurgles" premium subscriber.
你居然如此单纯地以为大家能顺从你的计划
You make a simple rule. You expect people to follow it.
盖比  她才两岁  她摒不住的
Gabe, she's  two. She can't hold it.
我们现在能转过身了吗
Can we turn around now
不行 再等会儿
Actually, give me a second.
什么状况
Unbelievable.
这样  你能继续把故事讲完吗
All right, would you please just finish the story?
你还是没告诉我们你是怎么进来的
You still haven't told us how you got arrested.
好吧  我们接着就去了酒店
All right, so we went down to the hotel.
嗯  我是423房的斯坦
Yeah, this is stan in 423.
我找不到我的遥控器了
I can't find my remote control.
噢  这回不在我屁股下
No, I'm not sitting on it again.
算了
Never mind.
门开着的
It's open.
我不敢相信 哇这真的是你
I can't believe it. It's you!
你就是那个圆圈啊
You're the circle!
问我要签名的话  五美元
You want me to sign something... Five bucks.
用金笔签  十美元
You want it in sparkly pen, it's 10 bucks.
噢不是  我们不是来要签名的
No no, we're not here for autographs.
我们想要演唱会的票
We want to ask about concert tickets.
-我们特地给你带了炸鸡排  -哈
- And we brought chicken. - Huh?
等下  等下  慢着
Whoa whoa whoa, wait a minute.
这是其他组员给你们出的主意吗
The other gurgles put you up to this?
来考验我节食节得怎么样了
Are they testing me to see if I'll stay on my diet?
考验你
Testing you?
组员们难道都不互相关爱互相帮助吗
Don't all the shapes love each other and help each other out?
-嗯  嗯  是的  -尝尝看
- Yeah yeah, that's it. - Here you go.
-你有票子吗  -没有  你是想拉赞助商来吗
- So do you have any tickets? - No. You have any sides?
不给票我们就不给你吃鸡排
No ticky, no chicky.
PJ我们走吧  找个更好说话的组员
P.J., come on, let's go find a more helpful shape.
我马上跟来
I'll catch up with you.
听我说句  小圆
Listen, circ.
-嘿  我能叫你小圆吗  -不可以
- Heh, can I call you circ? - No.
唉  好吧 事实上我也是做音乐的
Uh, well, the thing is I am a musician
我给咯咯笑组合写了首很赞的歌
and I wrote a song that is perfect for the gurgles.
-你想听听看吗  -噢不了  谢谢
- You wanna hear it? - No no no, thanks.
我们所有的歌都是三角写的
Triangle writes all our songs
他简直是个天才
'cause he's a genius.
只占你一分钟嘛  就一分钟
This will only take a minute, only take a minute.
这是首  这是首我创作于
This is a song... This is a song I wrote
我擦破膝盖后的歌
after I skinned my knee.
当你伤口结了疤你有何所得
What do you get when you pick a scab?
结了疤  结了疤
Pick a scab, pick a scab.
当你伤口结了疤你有何所得
What do you get when you pick a scab?
那疤痕永远也去不掉了
A scar that lasts forever.
想再听一首吗
you wanna hear another one?
不  听着  孩子  我只想一个人呆一会儿
No. Look, kid, I just want to be left alone
看看电视  明白吗
and watch tv, okay?
呃  我晕
Aw, nuts.
嘿  我一会儿回来
Okay, I'll be back in a little while.
-你去哪儿啊  -开车带马出去转转
- Where are you going? - Taking the horse for a drive.
我想看看当人们看见
I like to see people's faces
它把头伸出窗外时的表情
when he sticks his tiny head out the window.
噢  鲍伯  快出来看啊  马不见了
Oh! Bob, get out here! The horse is gone.
我们的牲口被抢了  该死
We've been rustled? Dag nabbit!
你确定你要这么干吗
you sure you wanna do this?
我也不觉得溜进演唱会这主意有多好
I don't like the idea of sneaking into a concert,
可是没什么其他办法了  我不想让查莉失望
but there's no way I'm gonna let Charlie down.
更何况  最坏又能怎么样
And besides, what's the worst that could happen?
他们又不可能把我们抓进去
It's not like they're gonna throw us in jail.
好了  别笑了  开始酝酿悲伤
Okay, stop laughing. It's time to get sad.
想些无比悲痛的事
Think of something really sad.
好啊  哈  真不错
Okay. Oh, that's good.
-想下那条狗  -你好小狗
- Thinking of hey there, poochy?  - Howdy puppy.
-下一位  -嗨
- Next. - Hi.
-请出示门票  -情况是这样的
- Ticket, please. - Um, quick story.
-非常悲伤的一件事  -让我猜猜
- It's actually pretty sad. - Let me guess.
你设法给你
You're trying to get tickets for your baby sister
咯咯笑组合的世界头粉小妹妹弄张门票
who's the biggest gurgles fan in the whole world
可票却买光了
and they were sold out,
现在你想让我放你们进去
and now you want me to just let you guys in?
别把真相说出来行吗
It's even sadder when you say it.
结果比真相还糟
And here's the saddest thing of all.
下一位
Next!
下面得出狠招了
Time to kick it up a notch.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- Ready? - Ready.
噢  噢  噢
Oh oh oh!
快救救他呀  那个男孩晕倒了
Help help! That boy just collapsed!
别担心  我是医生
It's okay. I'm a doctor.
-我知道怎么给他人工呼吸  -我没事了
- I know mouth to mouth. - All better.
嗨  我叫鲍伯  臭虫害虫灭光光
Hi, I'm Bob... Bob's bugs be gone.
来这儿处理后台火蚁的问题
I'm here about the fire ant problem backstage.
职业除虫家  是吗
Exterminators, huh?
那为何手上抱着着婴儿呢
Why do you have a baby with you?
她跟着来实习的
She's an intern.
-你还真当我蠢货吗  -不是
- You really think I'm that stupid? - No.
-嘿 看那儿啊  -什么
- Hey, look over there. - What?
嘿
Hey!
需要帮助吗
Can I help you?
-我是动物管理协会的  -很好
- Animal control. - Good.
你的脸怎么了
What happened to your face?
花栗鼠只有在卡通里才是可爱的  夫人
Chipmunks are only cute in cartoons, ma'am.
这是你们的马吗
Is this your horse?
-是啊  你找到了他  -天哪
- Yes. You found him! - Hey!
我的神啊  我们担心坏了
Oh my gosh, we've been worried sick.
-他现在在哪儿啊  -不要急
- Where is he? - Not so fast.
恐怕这匹马是偷来的
I'm afraid this animal is stolen proper.
什么  我们没有偷过马
What? We didn't steal it.
我丈夫把它租来给女儿办生日派对的
My husband rented it for our daughter's birthday party.
请给我看下租约
Just show me the rental agreement,
你们就没事了
we can clear this right up.
可是我没有租约
I haven't got a rental agreement.
那人只给我伸了双汗手
I got a sweaty handshake
然后坐着黑面包车就扬长而去了
and he took off in his dark van.
我感觉应该可以了
Seemed okay to me.
那恐怕你们逃不掉麻烦了
Then I'm afraid we have a problem.
噢不  不  不  亲
No no no, hon.
你的租约在这儿呀
Here's your rental agreement.
亲爱的  我告诉过你我没有的
Honey, I told you I didn't get one.
噢不  就在这儿嘛  是的是的
Oh no, it's right here. Yeah yeah.
事实上
As a matter of fact,
他有两张租约
he has two rental agreements.
您企图贿赂我吗  夫人
Are you trying to bribe me, ma'am?
我们还有蛋糕呢
We also have cake.
我们就这么被抓了进来
So that's how we got here,
就剩PJ没有说了
which only leaves P.J.
你怎么被抓进来的
How did you get here?
哈  其实说来真逗
Oh, cute story, actually.
演唱会结束后
So it was after the concert.
亏我还是在耶鲁上的大学
I can't believe I went to Yale.
如今却沦落至此
Now I'm a gurgle.
我有会说话的脚趾头
<i>I've got talkin' toes</i>
大脚趾爱说你好
<i>The big one likes to say hello</i>
其他四个很腼腆
<i>The other four are not so bold</i>
天冷时  他们蜷在一起
<i>They curl up when it gets too cold.</i>
你太有才了  孩子
That's great, kid.
噢  你喜欢那首吗  我还有好多其他的呢
Oh, you like that one? I've got plenty of others...
有首关于会说话的眼睛  还有首是会说话的膝盖
One about talking eyes, one about talking knees...
好吧   你就没有首写保安的吗
Yeah, do you happen to have a song about security guards?
这可不是什么好主意
That's not a good idea for a song.
天哪
Oh.
一会见喽  我要去监狱了
<i>See you later, I'm off to jail</i>
一会能帮我交保释金吗
<i>Could you do me a favor and post my bail?</i>
这个咯咯笑组员上过耶鲁大学...
<i>Here's a gurgle</i><i>who went to Yale... </i>
因此我因骚扰咯咯笑组合成员被逮捕
so I was busted for harassing a gurgle
同时被踢出了粉丝俱乐部
and stripped of my membership from the fan club.
好了  邓肯一家  你们可以走了
Okay, Duncans, you're free to go.
你们被保释了
You've been bailed out.
-保释  -谁保的
- Bailed out? - By who?
圆圈咯咯
Gurgle circle.
不错不错  这是你们人生中最美好的时刻
Yeah yeah, biggest moment of your life.
可你为什么保我们出去
But why did you bail us out?
嗯  我为其他几位咯咯成员
Well, I played "pick a scab"
弹唱了"伤疤歌"他们都说喜欢
for the other gurgles and they loved it.
-我卖出了一首歌  -不  是我
- I sold a song? - No, i sold a song.
你被保释了  娱乐圈随时欢迎你  孩子
You got bailed out. Welcome to showbiz, kid.
你知道吗  我挺怀念这儿的
You know, I'm gonna miss this place.
噢  别担心  你会有机会回来的
Oh, don't worry, you'll be back.
好了  查莉  你的两岁生日
Well, Charlie, your second birthday
最后过得如此有纪念意义
turned out to be pretty memorable...
比我两岁生日光辉多了  这是肯定的
More memorable than my second birthday, that's for sure.
现在说这个为时过早
Still too soon.
总之  你没机会看咯咯笑组合的演唱会了
Anyways, you never did get to see the gurgles in concert,
不过没关系因为你另有所爱了
but that's okay because you have a new favorite show.
噢  "毛毛组合"
Ooh, "the buttercups!"
如果你想看毛毛组合的演唱会
But if you ever wanna see the buttercups in concert,
得祝你好运了  查莉
good luck, Charlie.
嘘  这是新出来的
Shh! This is a new one.
嘿爸爸  我能带查莉出去策马奔腾下吗
Hey, dad, do you mind if I take Charlie out for a spin?
噢  抱歉  盖比
Ooh, sorry, Gabe.
我们现在没有马了
We don't have the horse anymore.
但我们可有车啊
But we do have the cart.
快一点
Faster!
看镜头  说"茄子"
Okay, say "Cheese."
站起来继续前进
Giddy up.
哇  你们出去了好久
Wow. You guys were gone a long time.
真的吗  我感觉才过了三十秒
Really? Seems like 30 seconds.
噢  你们看到什么有趣的东西了吗
Oh! Did you see anything interesting?
没  收了堆罚单而已
No, just a bunch of credits.